Ah
disappeared again
It's definitely nearby
I wouldn't have been able to run away
Let's spread out and search
I'll go this way
uh uh future
I uh I I
Oh, I'm surprised.
Ah
It's okay
I guess you couldn't find it
If I had seen it, I would have come to work.
I guess I ran away because I was scared anyway.
What's wrong
It's not strange
What is a devil?
It used to be visible only at night.
Now it appears all the time
The numbers continue to increase
don't worry too much
Tomorrow with the kids again
Let's look around
How long will we sit there?
I have to go back and join the kids.
uh
you go first
alone
why are you
You postpone it
I wonder if we are still meeting
I told you to stop
How long will this be my problem?
I'll take care of it
you can take care of it on your own
It's not a problem
What excuse do you make to the kids?
Taesan and Marge
What are you going to do if you find out?
It's Miru
think carefully
I keep secretly ignoring opportunities like this
When we meet, more than you
It's bigger for Ogi
harm will happen
I never thought about it
come with you
I hope we make choices for each other
Pretending not to know
Because this is the last time
It's Miru
don't forget
Ogi is different from us.
he is human
we are
Born to protect humans
If it's dangerous, just run away.
I'll handle it
are you ignoring me
Or are you doing it for the sake of others?
The only power is sealed
I'm the only one who didn't make it
I don't know haha
Just trust me
Oh really
Wow, you're good
Okay
uh
Samina
Did you take my eternity?
This happy face is here too
Hey, I'm worried
It's a really happy thought
Who should I kill first?
Miriam
Miri, there, there
Hey Miri
Miriam
Hahaha
Oh well
My memories came back haha
How are you?
My body doesn't move
Because my mind is fine
Despite being trapped for thousands of years
I couldn't get used to it even for a day.
Why did you seal me then?
that's not my plan
It's God's will
Your god who ignored me all my life
Are you talking about
Then the reason I ignore you is
How about
darkness for thousands of years
My time trapped inside
Like my memories that disappeared
to death
What should the captain say?
hello inspiration
inspiration
Ah, I
It hurts a lot
What happened to inspiration?
From now on
listen carefully to what i say
A merchant
I think I got the ETM
now
humans
I'll adjust it however I want
So
oh my god you
We must open the gates of hell
Okay
A world without humans
no future
It's going to be hell.
Oh please
and
Oh come on
I went in for a taste
That beauty
I must find it
already in the body
Even the dragon soul
If Samin goes
Even if your strength comes back
You won't be impressed.
Okay, okay, okay, old man.
I will definitely find beauty
I'm on my way now so just a little bit
Hang in there, old man
Ah, as an inspiration until the end
I wanted to kill more
To you, the ambassador
spitting
crab
my person
I
i borrowed it from you
borrowed money
Should I try it again?
Inspiration, pay back the money
Live and pay the money back
Come to your senses, brother.
to me
rely on and lean on
I'm sorry
why
Ha why bro
Brother
glory
here
Won Seung Ah
I have to go quickly
let's go quickly
Hey there
That's right
uh uh
Uh ha
ha
Ha ha
Captain Maru Maruge
ha
uh
Hahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha
Ugh
Ugh uh huh
Ugh, stop, stop, stop
mom
mom mom grandmother
Why
Now the world has returned to its own light
Humans are definitely
You must be something special
To remember the moments we spent together
Put your heads together
Join forces
for the dead
Build a stone tomb like this
To protect those people
God
I sent it to you and the angels in human form.
In the end what
God willing, you and the angels
Saved the human world
my brothers are dead
until we die
protecting humans
Is that really God's will?
To protect humans
Sacrifice is second to none
that
Accepting life is our destiny
prenatal baby
Because of the death of my brothers
I know you should never be shaken
What a miserable fate.
Blurred senses
This familiar subtlety is an illusion
Yesterday becomes a knife that stabs me
It broke me who hid my desires
My heart is in a new place
Yes my heart is a new wealth
forget amy
That bell lasts forever
Ugh
Seeing the things disappearing inside the two of us
I am now
with you
captain
Ha, what if the gates of hell are opened?
It won't break anyway
broken
now
The gates of hell are broken
The world will be covered with evil
just one day
Looking for Mir inside
I have to kill Samin and Ohgi.
and
Seal the gates of hell again
For currently unknown reasons, the sky
all black
Getting covered
As if it were night
It's getting dark
as well as
unidentified
Fine dust falls from the sky
There is a lot of damage around here.
Right now
Everyone who listened to the broadcast
For example, evacuate
Oh what
Oh, come out quickly, why?
Somebody is right
Ah, why are my uncles getting hit?
Oh, I'm not really crazy.
I need to go home
just eat something
you you you you you
Ah
let's go
captain
That's enough
Hye-tae turned into a demon.
I have to get off
That's God's will
Roll it up
It's okay.
Ugh
No
Blurred senses
This is a familiar illusion of an American drama
Yesterday becomes a knife that stabs me
I can't trust anyone
My heart is frozen with no place to lean on
It broke me who hid my desires
My heart is a drum made of iron
Yes, my heart is a drum made of iron
This is all I have
foot foot follow foot foot
I'm afraid now
Get out of debt for a little while
I was shaking in the fan room for a little while
Trembling along
My burning fist is Red Bell Run Wolwol
blazing fist
Grab the sword that cuts through the darkness, thump thump
The dove splits the darkness
Quick quick, even if I look back, I can’t turn back.
crazy fight
Reflected in tired eyes
The chromatic layer peeled off and smeared on both fists
Three fireworks and fire fire
I'm Tiger is far away
Even if I try to run, the punishment is overshadowed
Chaechae Eating Black Meat Anchaechae